wpremote.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy - WP Remote

### 1\. Information that we collect and store

#### Registration information

We store the minimum possible personal information. When you register for an account with WP Remote you are asked to provide a valid email address and account password.

#### Website domain names

We collect and store the domain names of any domains that are added to your WP Remote account.

#### Website data files

If you have opted for us to backup your sites we create and store backup copies of your website files and database for any selected domains at the intervals that you specify. We never ask for any information that would allow us to access or edit the content of your websites such as user names or passwords.

#### Payment card information

If you have opted for us to backup your sites we collect payment card information. This information is collected and stored securely by our trusted third party payment gateway provider. We do not have direct access to your payment card information.

#### Cookies

We use “cookies” to collect information and improve our website services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your device. We use “persistent cookies” to save your registration email and login password for future logins to the WP Remote website. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to take full advantage of all aspects of the website.

### 2\. How we use your information

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected and do not share your information with anyone except to provide you with support for the WP Remote service, protect our rights or unless we are required to by law.

#### Administration and support

Email information is used for the purposes of site log-in and administration and for the provision of support services in response to a request via the site feedback form.

On your request we may access website backup files as part of our support services, however this is limited to viewing or copying the backup zip-file itself and will never include modifying the file or accessing the backup file content.

#### Trusted service providers

We use Amazon S3 to provide our data storage service. You can find more information on Amazon’s data security from the[ S3 site](http://aws.amazon.com/security/ "Amazon S3").

We use Stripe as our merchant payment gateway provider.

#### Non-private or non-personal information.

We may disclose non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our service.

### 3\. Changing or deleting your information

As a registered user of WP Remote you may log on to the service and change your stored password, add additional websites to your account or delete existing websites from your account at any time.

As a user of WP Remote Automatic Backups you may also log on to the service and change your payment card information at any time.

### 4\. Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you delete a website from your account, all backup data files held from that site will automatically be deleted. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us at support@wpremote.com. We will try to delete your information quickly upon request.

### 5\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information and data is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. This is outlined in further detail in our [WP Remote security ](https://wpremote.com/security/ "Security")document.

### 6\. Business Transfer

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your personal information or files, or if either become subject to a different privacy policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information

### 7\. Changes to our privacy policy

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 10th February 2012.

Latest update 05-06-13.
